func nextQuestion() {
    currentQuestion += 1

    var newQuestion: AnyObject = arrayOfQuestions[currentQuestion]
    questionCorrectAnswer = newQuestion[9].integerValue

    firstAnswer.hidden = false
    secondAnswer.hidden = false
    thirdAnswer.hidden = false
    fourthAnswer.hidden = false

    firstAnswer.setTitle("\(newQuestion[1])", forState: UIControlState.Normal)
    secondAnswer.setTitle("\(newQuestion[2])", forState: UIControlState.Normal)
    thirdAnswer.setTitle("\(newQuestion[3])", forState: UIControlState.Normal)
    fourthAnswer.setTitle("\(newQuestion[4])", forState: UIControlState.Normal)

    questionLabel.text = "\(newQuestion[0])"

    myNextQuestion.hidden = true

}

var newQuestion : AnyObject = arrayOfQuestions[currentQuestion]

    let firstQuestion :AnyObject = Question(question: "What was the first planet to be discovered using a telescope, in 1781?", answerOne: "Mars", answerTwo: "Jupiter", answerThree: "Uranus", answerFour: "Mercury", correctAnswer: 3)
    let secondQuestion = Question(question: "Who averaged 1 patent for every three weeks of his life?", answerOne: "Ben Franklin", answerTwo: "Thomas Edison", answerThree: "Henry Ford", answerFour: "Ezra Gilliland", correctAnswer: 2)
    let thirdQuestion = Question(question: "Which island is the world's largest island?", answerOne: "Iceland", answerTwo: "Australia", answerThree: "Hawaii", answerFour: "Greenland", correctAnswer: 4)
    let fourthQuestion = Question(question: "What is the diameter of the Earth?", answerOne: "5,000 Miles", answerTwo: "6,000 Miles", answerThree: "8,000 Miles", answerFour: "10,000 Miles", correctAnswer: 3)
    let fifthQuestion = Question(question: "The US is the world's 5th largest producer of potatoes. What are the two top potato producing countries?", answerOne: "Canada/Italy", answerTwo: "China/Russa", answerThree: "China/Spain", answerFour: "Hawaii/Russia", correctAnswer: 2)
    let sixthQuestion = Question(question: "What is the symbol for iron on the periodic table?", answerOne: "Fe", answerTwo: "Ne", answerThree: "Se", answerFour: "Io", correctAnswer: 1)
    let seventhQuestion = Question(question: "The Hubble Telescope is named after which astronomer?", answerOne: "Frank Hubble", answerTwo: "Timothy Hubble", answerThree: "Edwin Hubble", answerFour: "Roger Hubble", correctAnswer: 3)
    let eighthQuestion = Question(question: "What year did the Apple's first iPhone become available?", answerOne: "2007", answerTwo: "2005", answerThree: "2005", answerFour: "2003", correctAnswer: 1)
    let ninethQuestion = Question(question: "OS computer abbreviation usually means what?", answerOne: "Optical Sensor", answerTwo: "Operating System", answerThree: "Open Software", answerFour: "Operating Sensor", correctAnswer: 2)
    let tenthQuestion = Question(question: "Where was the first mouse designed?", answerOne: "Apple", answerTwo: "Microsoft", answerThree: "Xerox", answerFour: "Hewlett-Packard", correctAnswer: 3)

    //Array of Questions Set

    arrayOfQuestions = [firstQuestion, secondQuestion, thirdQuestion, fourthQuestion, fifthQuestion, sixthQuestion, seventhQuestion, eighthQuestion, ninethQuestion, tenthQuestion]

